A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, National Commission on Water Quality, Series 9 FA379
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Regional - Delaware River Basin (Contract with Betz Environmental Eng.) (Box 6, Folder 209)
- Regional - Houston Ship Channel / Galveston Bay (Contract with Bernard Johnson, Inc.) (Box 6, Folder 210)
- Regional - Hudson River (Box 6, Folder 211)
  See environmental impact section
- Regional - Lake Erie (Contract with Dalton, Dalton, Little & Newport) (Box 6, Folder 212)
- Regional - Ohio River Basin (Contract with Daimes & Moore) (Box 6, Folder 213)
- Regional - Puget Sound / Lake Washington (Contract with Stevens, Thompson & Ruuyan) (Box 6, Folder 214)
- Regional - San Francisco Bay / Central Valley (Contract with Arthur Little, Inc.) (Box 6, Folder 215)
- Regional - Yellowstone River Basin (Contract with Stevens, Thompson & Ruuyan) (Box 6, Folder 216)
- Regional - Economic / Social / Benefits / Institutional Inputs (Box 6, Folder 217)
- Regional - 9 Field Meetings to Announce Regional Assessment Studies (Box 6, Folder 218)
- Regional - Agendas (Commission and Executive Committee Meetings), 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 219)
- Regional - Minutes (Commission and Executive Committee Meetings), 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 220)
- Meetings - Staff - Governor's Mansion, Albany, May 7, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 221)
- Meetings - First Commission Meeting, May 15, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 222)
- Meetings - Transcript, May 15, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 223)
- Meetings - Ross Perot and New York State Officials, 812 Fifth Avenue, New York, May 23, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 224)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, May 30, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 225)
- Meetings - Second Commission Meeting, June 7, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 226)
- Meetings - Transcript, June 7, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 227)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, June 21, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 228)
- Meetings - Third Commission Meeting, July 12, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 229)
- Meetings - Transcript, July 12, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 229)
- Meetings - Fourth Commission Meeting, July 31, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 231)
- Meetings - Transcript, July 31, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 232)
- Meetings - August 15-16, 1973 (Top Staff, Boston); August 17, 1973 (Staff with NAR, Seal Harbor, Maine), August, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 233)
- Meetings - D. Mitchell with NAR, New York, New York, September 12, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 234)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, Hay Adams, Washington, September 24, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 235)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, September 26, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 236)
- Meetings - Fifth Commission Meeting, October 4, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 237)
- Meetings - Transcript, October 4, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 238)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, New York City, November 20, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 239)
- Meetings - Sixth Commission Meeting, December 6, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 240)
- Meetings - Transcript, December 6, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 241)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, Clark & Mitchell, Room 5600, New York, December 21, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 242)
- Meetings - Mailing to Commission, December 21, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 243)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, January 24, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 244)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, Breakfast, 2400 Foxhall Road, DC, February 7, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 245)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, February 26, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 246)
- Meetings - Seventh Commission Meeting, March 7, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 247)
- Meetings - Transcript, March 7, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 248)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, April 9, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 249)
- Meetings - Eighth Commission Meeting, April 24, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 250)
- Meetings - Transcript, April 24, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 251)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, May 22, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 252)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, May 29, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 253)
- Meetings - Ninth Commission Meeting, June 6, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 254)
- Meetings - Transcript, June 6, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 255)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, June 26, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 256)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, July 18, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 257)
- Meetings - Tenth Commission Meeting, July 25, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 258)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, August 13, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 259)
- Meetings - Briefing of Commission, October 11, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 260)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, November 21, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 261)
- Meetings - Eleventh Commission Meeting, November 26, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 262)
- Meetings - Transcript, November 26, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 263)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, January 21, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 264)
- Meetings - Twelfth Commission Meeting, February 20, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 265)
- Meetings - Transcript, February 20, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 266)
- Meetings - Dinner with Public Members, 2500 Foxhall Road, March 5, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 267)
- Meetings - Briefing of Commission and Outside Groups, March 6, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 268)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, March 25, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 269)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, April 7, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 270)
- Meetings - Thirteenth Commission Meeting, April 8, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 271)
- Meetings - Transcript, April 8, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 272)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, April 23, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 273)
- Meetings - Briefing of Commission and Outside Groups, April 29, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 274)
- Meetings - Fourteenth Commission Meeting, May 8, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 275)
- Meetings - Transcript, May 8, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 276)
- Meetings - Briefing of Commission and Outside Groups, May 20, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 277)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, May 29, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 278)
- Meetings - Fifteenth Commission Meeting, June 16, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 279)
- Meetings - Transcript, June 16, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 280)
- Meetings - Sixteenth Commission Meeting, July 15, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 281)
- Meetings - Transcript, July 15, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 282)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, July 30, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 283)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, September 3, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 284)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, September 9, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 285)
- Meetings - Meetings General, September-October, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 286)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, September 24, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 287)
- Meetings - Seventeenth Commission Meeting, September 25, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 288)
- Meetings - Transcript, September 25, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 289)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, October 6, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 290)
- Meetings - Eighteenth Commission Meeting, October 10, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 291)
- Meetings - Transcript, October 10, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 292)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, October 20, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 293)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, October 28, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 294)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, November 3, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 295)
- Meetings - Executive Committee - Transcript Included, November 12, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 296)
- Meetings - Meetings - General, November 1975 - March 1976 (Box 8, Folder 297)
- Meetings - Executive Committee, December 4, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 298)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, January 21 and 28, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 299)
- Meetings - Nineteenth Commission Meeting - Dinner, 2500 Foxhall Road, February 17, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  No transcript
- Meetings - Twentieth Commission Meeting, February 19, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 301)
- Meetings - Transcript, February 19, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 302)
- Meetings - Twenty-first Commission Meeting, February 24, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 303)
- Meetings - Transcript, February 24, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 304)
- Meetings - Twenty-second (and final) Commission Meeting, March 2, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 305)
- Meetings - Transcript, March 2, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 306)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, March 16, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 307)
- Meetings - NAR with Staff, April 28, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 308)
- Public Affairs - Liaison with States, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  NAR letter to Governors, October 3, 1973, and responses
- Public Affairs - Plan for Liaison with Outside Groups and EPA (Box 8, Folder 310)
- Public Affairs - Newspaper Clippings (Box 8, Folder 311)
- Public Affairs - Digests of Press Clippings, June 12, 1974 to July 16, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 312)
- Public Affairs - Meetings with Outside Groups; Dept. and Agency Attendance; NCWQ Briefings, June 12, 1974 to July 16, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 313)
- Public Affairs - Meetings: Puiblic (Overall and Policy), November 19, 1973 to December 16, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 314)
- Meetings with States, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 315)
  See separate folders for January-February 1974 meetings around country.
- Meetings with States - Boston (Northeast - New England), January 22, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 316)
- Meetings with States - Washington (Mid-Atlantic), January 23, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 317)
- Meetings with States - Denver (Colorado region), January 28, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 318)
- Meetings with States - Chicago (Great Lakes), January 29, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 319)
- Meetings with States - St. Louis (Missouri Basin), January 30, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 320)
- Meetings with States - Dallas (Lower Mississippi), January 31, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 321)
- Meetings with States - Atlanta (South Atlantic; Gulf), February 1, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 322)
- Meetings with States - Seattle (Pacific Northwest), February 21, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 323)
- Meetings - Technical (Boston), February 18 and 19, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 324)
- Meetings - Technical (Los Angeles), April 3 and 4, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 325)
- Meetings - Technical (New Orleans), April 25 and 26, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 326)
- Meetings - Technical (Kansas City), May 14 and 15, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 327)
- Meetings - Technical (Portland, OR), May 27 and 28, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 328)
- Meetings - Technical (Chicago), June 17 and 18, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 329)
- Meetings - Technical (Atlanta), July 9 and 10, 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 330)
- Meetings - Technical (Atlanta), July 9 and 10, 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 331)
- Meetings - Business Round Table, May 2, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 332)
- Meetings - Outside Groups with NAR (Chemical Industry), July 31, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 333)
- Meetings - Technical (Steam Electric Power), September 19, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 334)
- Meetings - Outside Groups with NAR (Industrial Community), September 10, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 335)
- Meetings - Outside Groups with NAR (Environmentalists), October 1, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 336)
- Meetings - Outside Groups with NAR (State Representatives), September 29, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 337)
- Meetings - Outside Groups with NAR (State Representatives, "Committee of Ten"), November 5, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 338)
- Speeches - Requests to NAR (Box 9, Folder 339)
- Speeches - Given by NAR (Box 9, Folder 340)
- Speeches - Tad Schad Before WPCF, October 3, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 341)
- Speeches - Staff (Box 9, Folder 342)
- Speeches - Awards to NAR (Box 9, Folder 343)
- Contracts - Alphabetical and Numerical Listing; Inventory & Status; Contract Releases; Publications List (Box 9, Folder 344)
- Contracts - Abt Associates (River Basin: Merrimack) (Box 9, Folder 345)
- Contracts - Abt Associates (Social Impacts) (Box 9, Folder 346)
- Contracts - Academy of Natural Sciences, Philadelphia (Env. water sites) (Box 9, Folder 347)
- Contracts - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations (Economic) (Box 9, Folder 348)
- Contracts - American Public Works Association (On Needs Survey) (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 349)
- Contracts - American Water Works Association Research Foundation (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 350)
- Contracts - Arthur D. Little, Inc. (2-Regional) (Box 9, Folder 351)
- Contracts - Association of Metropolitan Sewerage Agencies (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 352)
- Contracts - Atlantic Scientific (Environmental) (Box 9, Folder 353)
- Contracts - Battelle Memorial Institute (2-Economic) (Box 9, Folder 354)
- Contracts - Bernard Johnson, Inc. (Regional) (Box 9, Folder 355)
- Contracts - Betz Environmental Engineers, Inc. (Regional) (Box 9, Folder 356)
- Contracts - Beychock, Milton R. (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 357)
- Contracts - Black, Crow & Eidsness (Urban Runoff) (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 358)
- Contracts - Boeing Computer Services, Inc. (Economic) (Box 9, Folder 359)
- Contracts - Bureau of National Affairs - Legal Study (Institutional) (Box 9, Folder 360)
- Contracts - Burt, Dr. Oscar R. (Economic) (Box 9, Folder 361)
- Contracts - University of California (Irrigated Agriculture) (Technology) (Box 9, Folder 362)
- Contracts - Catalytic, Inc. (Organic Chemicals) (Box 9, Folder 363)
- Contracts - Center for Environment & Man, Inc. (Economic and Social) (Environmental) (Box 9, Folder 364)
- Contracts - Coastal Ecosystems Management, Inc. (Environmental Water Site) (Box 9, Folder 365)
- Contracts - The Conference Board (Economic) (2) (Box 9, Folder 366)
- Contracts - CONSAD Research Corp (Economic, SEAS) (Box 9, Folder 367)
- Contracts - Control Data Corp (Economic Impact; SEAS; SEAS III System Integration) (2) (Box 10, Folder 368)
- Contracts - Cook, Howard L. - Consultant $10,000 (Box 10, Folder 369)
- Contracts - Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport - River Basin: Lake Erie - $285,000 (Box 10, Folder 370)
- Contracts - Dames & Moore, Inc. - River Basin: Kanawha - $225,000 (Box 10, Folder 371)
- Contracts - Dames & Moore, Inc. - River Basin: Ohio - $211,000 (Box 10, Folder 372)
- Contracts - Data Resources, Inc. - State / Local Finances - $69,600 (Box 10, Folder 373)
- Contracts - Development Planning & Research Association - Economic Impacts (Agriculture Industry) - $175,000 (Box 10, Folder 374)
- Contracts - Development Planning & Research Association - Feedlots - $50,000 (Box 10, Folder 375)
- Contracts - David M. Dornbosch & Co. - Economic Impact - Property Valuation - $140,000 (Box 10, Folder 376)
- Contracts - Downing, Donald L. - Consultant - Fruits and Vegetables - $2500 (Box 10, Folder 377)
- Contracts - Electronic Data Systems - First Overview (Ross Perot) - $75,000 (Box 10, Folder 378)
- Contracts - Energy & Environmental Analysis Inc. - Institutional: Permits - $125,000 (Box 10, Folder 379)
- Contracts - Energy Resources Co. Inc. - Institutional: Monitoring - $71,150 (Box 10, Folder 380)
- Contracts - Engineering-Science, Inc. - Ocean Disposal - $14,115 (Box 10, Folder 381)
- Contracts - Engineering-Science, Inc. - Austin - Petroleum & Refining - $168,000 (Box 10, Folder 382)
- Contracts - Environmental Analysts, Inc. - Environmental Site (Chicago) - $50,000 (Box 10, Folder 383)
- Contracts - Environmental Associates - Fruits & Vegetables Industry - $182,000 (Box 10, Folder 384)
- Contracts - Environmental Dynamics, Inc. - Environmental Site: Utah - $50,000 (Box 10, Folder 385)
- Contracts - Environmental Law Institute - Institutional: Enforcement - $127,500 (Box 10, Folder 386)
- Contracts - Environmental Quality Systems - Intermedia Transfer - $230,000 (Box 10, Folder 387)
- Contracts - Fisher, Anthony - Consultant - $2,500 (Box 10, Folder 388)
- Contracts - Florida State University - Economic Impact (Coastal Area Fisheries) - $107,914 (Box 10, Folder 389)
- Contracts - GKY Assoc. - Regional: Evaluation of Reports - Kanawha & Ohio - $3,000 (Box 10, Folder 390)
- Contracts - GKY Assoc. - Environmental Water Site - $15,433 (Box 10, Folder 391)
- Contracts - Hammer, Siler & George Associates - River Basin: Chattahoochee-Flint-Apalachicola - $200,000 (Box 10, Folder 392)
- Contracts - Hartley, David K. - Consultant - Institutional "Doers" - $12,000 (Box 10, Folder 393)
- Contracts - Haskell, Elizabeth - Consultant - Institutional - $2,000 (Box 10, Folder 394)
- Contracts - Hazen & Sawyer - New York City Pulp and Paper - $173,000 (Box 10, Folder 395)
- Contracts - Human Resource Planning - Social Impact Site Studies - $42,230 (Box 10, Folder 396)
- Contracts - Inerfield, Arthur J. & Assoc. - Institutional Assistance - $5,000 (Box 10, Folder 397)
- Contracts - Hydroscience, Inc. - Environmental Site Analysis - $56,115 (Box 10, Folder 398)
- Contracts - The Institute of Ecology - $131,552 (Box 10, Folder 399)
- Contracts - Inter-industry Economic Research Fund (SEAS) - $15,000 (Box 10, Folder 400)
- Contracts - International Research & Technology Corp. - Economic Impact - Chemicals Industry - $192,500 (Box 10, Folder 401)
- Contracts - International Research & Technology - Economic Impact - SEAS Technology Change and Inside Expansion - $65,000 (Box 10, Folder 402)
- Contracts - Iowa State: Center for Agricultural & Rural Development - Economic Impacts: Irrigated Agriculture - $41,000 (Box 10, Folder 403)
- Contracts - King, A. Thomas - Consultant - $2,000 (Box 10, Folder 404)
- Contracts - Klashman, Lester A. - Consultant - $1,000 (Box 10, Folder 405)
- Contracts - Lancy Laboratories - Electroplating Industry - $189,200 (Box 10, Folder 406)
- Contracts - Lawler, Matusky & Skelly - Environmental Water Sites - $103,460 (Box 10, Folder 407)
- Contracts - Lawler, Matusky & Skelly Eng. - Hudson - Env. Site - $69,700 (Box 10, Folder 408)
  See note on lawsuit in "Lawler" file.
- Contracts - Linton, Mields & Coston - Overall Study - Contract WQ3AC002: $36,000 - Contract WQ4AC008: $78,000 (Box 10, Folder 409)
- Contracts - Lockwood Greene - (Textile Industry Study) - $171,895 (Box 10, Folder 410)
- Contracts - Management Sciences Systems - Analysis of Agricultural Impact Studies - $3,000 (Box 10, Folder 411)
- Contracts - Masselli, Joseph W. - Consultant, Textiles - $2,800 (Box 10, Folder 412)
- Contracts - Arthur G. McGee, Cleveland, Iron & Steel - $220,000 (Box 10, Folder 413)
- Contracts - Meta Systems Inc. - Economic Impact - Municipal Effluents - $120,000 (Box 10, Folder 414)
- Contracts - Meta Systems Inc. - Environmental Water Sites - $46,566 (Box 10, Folder 415)
- Contracts - Metcalf & Eddy - (Municipal Technology Study) - $498,726 (Box 10, Folder 416)
- Contracts - Midwest Research Institute - Environmental Water Site - $72,500 (Box 10, Folder 417)
- Contracts - Midwest Research Institute - Non-point Sources - $35,000 (Box 10, Folder 418)
- Contracts - Miller, Perry - Consultant - Institutional "Doers" - $3,000 (Box 10, Folder 419)
- Contracts - National Academy of Sciences - $489,000 (Box 10, Folder 420)
- Contracts - NBER (National Bureau of Economic Research) - Commission Approved June 6, 1974 - $379,400 (Box 10, Folder 421)
- Contracts - National Planning Association - Economic Impact - Selected Mfg. - $89,000 (Box 10, Folder 422)
- Contracts - National Planning Association - Economics: Recreation - $192,500 (Box 11, Folder 423)
- Contracts - North Star Research & Development Institute - Environmental Water Site - $80,300 (Box 11, Folder 424)
- Contracts - Oregon Research Institute - Institutional: Attitudes - $119,400 (Box 11, Folder 425)
- Contracts - Parametrix, Inc. - Environmental Water Site - $69,130 (Box 11, Folder 426)
- Contracts - Price, Victoria - Consultant - Institutional: "Doers" - $10,000 (Box 11, Folder 427)
- Contracts - Process Research, Inc. - Environmental Water Site - $68,965 (Box 11, Folder 428)
- Contracts - Procon - (Synthetics and Plastics Study) - $171,254 (Box 11, Folder 429)
- Contracts - PIEC (Public Interest Economics Center) - $28,790 (Box 11, Folder 430)
- Contracts - Public Research Institute (Center for Naval Analyses) - Economic Impact - International Trade - $115,000 (Box 11, Folder 431)
- Contracts - Ragan (James) Associates - Institutional: Public Participation - $78,195 (Box 11, Folder 432)
- Contracts - Resources for the Future - $7,500 (Box 11, Folder 433)
- Contracts - Seneca, Joseph J. - Consultant - $5,000 (Box 11, Folder 434)
- Contracts - Smith, Dr. V. Kerry - Consultant - $7,500 (Box 11, Folder 435)
- Contracts - Southern California Coastal Water Research Project - $19,400 (Box 11, Folder 436)
- Contracts - Stevens, Thompson & Runyan, Inc. - River Basin: Yellowstone - $200,000 (Box 11, Folder 437)
- Contracts - Stevens, Thompson & Runyan, Inc. - River Basin: Puget Sound-Lake Washington - $215,000 (Box 11, Folder 438)
- Contracts - Teknekron - Steam Electric Power - $262,000 (Box 11, Folder 439)
- Contracts - TetraTech Inc. - Environmental Water Sites - $311,935 (Box 11, Folder 440)
- Contracts - Tippetts-Abbett-McCarthy-Stratton (General Clarke) - $197,000 (Box 11, Folder 441)
- Contracts - Touche Ross & Co. - Institutional: Construction Grants - $149,000 (Box 11, Folder 442)
- Contracts - Toups Corp. - Irrigation Return Flows - $75,000 (Box 11, Folder 443)
- Contracts - TRW, Inc. - Environmental Water Site - $49,400 (Box 11, Folder 444)
- Contracts - University of Texas, Austin (Dale Wittington, Consultant) - $6,400 (Box 11, Folder 445)
- Contracts - Urban Systems Research & Engineering, Cambridge, MA - Economic Impact - Direct Economic Incidence - $91,400 (Box 11, Folder 446)
- Contracts - Utah State University Foundation - River Basin: Colorado - $225,000 (Box 11, Folder 447)
- Contracts - University of Virginia - Economic: Computer - INFORUM and CONSAD - $10,000 (Box 11, Folder 448)
- Contracts - Vanderbilt University - Environmental Site: Percy Priest Reservoir - $50,000 (Box 11, Folder 449)
- Contracts - Virginia Institute of Marine Science - Environmental Water Site: Chesapeake Bay - $59,100 (Box 11, Folder 450)
- Contracts - Water Purification Associates - Innovative Technologies - $65,000 (Box 11, Folder 451)
  Contains transcript of proceedings of National Commission on Water Quality meeting of June 6, 1974.
- Contracts - Water Resources Engineers - Environmental Water Sites - $170,335 (Box 11, Folder 452)
- Contracts - Whitman, Dr. Ira L. - Institutional: Construction Grants & Permits - $2,000 (Box 11, Folder 453)
- Contracts - Whitman, Dr. Ira L. - Regional: Evaluation of Ohio & Kanawha - $3,000 (Box 11, Folder 454)
- Contracts - Wise, Harold F. - Institutional: Planning - $106,294 (Box 11, Folder 455)
- Contracts - Alphabetical List (Box 11, Folder 456)
- Contracts - Numerical Order - Costs (Box 11, Folder 457)
- Contracts - General (Box 11, Folder 458)
- Contracts - Contractor Reports - Publication Policy (Box 11, Folder 459)
- Contracts - Publications List (Box 11, Folder 460)
  Note: Also lists reports not published.
- Contracts - Contractor Reports - NTIS Publication (Box 11, Folder 461)
- Contracts - Administrative Procedures for Handling (Box 11, Folder 462)
  See Box #2 for consultant and contractor selection procedures.
- Contracts - Contract Disputes - Procedures (Box 11, Folder 463)
- Contracts - Deobligations (Box 11, Folder 464)
- Contracts - Contract Releases (Box 11, Folder 465)
- Contracts - Consultants (Program & Executive Directors Authority) (Box 11, Folder 466)
- Contracts - Contract Increases - Executive Director's Authority (discretionary) (Box 11, Folder 467)
- Contracts - Contractor Invoices Paid After April 16, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 468)
- Contracts - Contract Costs - By Program Area (Ref: Contract Inventory, July 1976) (Box 11, Folder 469)
- Contracts - Modifications (overall) (Box 11, Folder 470)
- Contracts - Overall Overruns (Box 11, Folder 471)
  See individual contractor files for specific cases.
- Contracts - Status Reports (Box 11, Folder 472)
- Contracts - Status of Reports, August 1975 (Box 11, Folder 473)
- Contracts - Inventory & Status, June 30, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 474)
- Contracts - Reports Stored at Interior Department (Box 11, Folder 475)
- Contracts - Status (during "budget crisis"), February 1976 (Box 11, Folder 476)
- Industries - Costs, McGraw-Hill Survey, May 1974, 1975, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 477)
- Industries - General, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 478)
- Industries - Chemical, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 479)
- Industries - Iron & Steel, 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 480)
- Industries - Iron & Steel - Mahoning Valley, Ohio, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 481)
- Industries - Mining, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 482)
- Industries - Petroleum Refining, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 483)
- Industries - Pulp and Paper, 1972, 1974, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 484)
- Industries - Pulp and Paper, Ketchikan, Alaska, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 485)
- Industries - Steam Electric Power, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 486)